

Matthew David Rodgers

843-327-4828 matthewdavidrodgers@gmail.com 155 Anderson Hwy , APT 310, Clemson SC, 29631

Profile

I am a creative and critical thinker with a professional and recreational interest in the entertainment industry and computer science. I have founded a film society, written multiple films, worked on advanced high profile web applications, and was the first runner up for a 24-hr hackathon.

Skills

Programming experience in C, C++, C#, Java, Javascript (Node.js and AngularJS), and Python

Script coverage and re-writes

Experience

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN, BLACKBAUD; MT PLEASANT - 2016-2016

At Blackbaud, I worked with some of the Southeast's best developers on a RESTful web api, as well as developing their new SKY UX front end framework. I also worked on a team that developed an android application and was the first runner up in a 24-hr hackathon.

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN, BENEFITFOCUS; MT PLEASANT – 2015-2015

I worked under an Agile development team for a high profile MVC web application, Fixing bugs and contributing original features.

SERVER, LA PIZZERIA; MT PLEASANT – 2015-2015

I spent a summer as a server in an Italian restaurant. I learned a lot about about communication there, as multiple languages and cultures were represented.

SERVER/EXPO MANAGER, TRIANGLE CHAR & BAR; MT PLEASANT – 2011-2014, 2016-2016

After starting as a server's assistant, I was quickly promoted to a sever. I was then promoted again to Expo Manager. Despite the hire/fire culture of the food and beverage industry, I learned much about loyalty during my time there.

Education

Wando High School, Mt. Pleasant, SC 2014: Focus on Java: work done with applets

Clemson University, Clemson, SC (current student): Focus on C/Java, Usable Privacy and Security, The Palmetto Supercomputer/Cyprus Hadoop Cluster, and Film/Screenwriting; Founded Clemson Cinema Club; Student Radio DJ

Deakin University, Melbourne, Australia 2016: Film and Computer Science study abroad student